<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
<dict>
	<key>ArchitecturalDrawing</key>
	<string>Complicated child-like architectural diagram</string>
	<key>AutumnLeaves</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of leaves from a deciduous tree during Autumn.</string>
	<key>BaseballHatSilhouette</key>
	<string>iPod Wallpaper with man wearing baseball hat silhouette</string>
	<key>BlackAndWhiteLakeAndHills</key>
	<string>A black and white photo of a lake bordered by hills. Storm clouds approach.</string>
	<key>BlackDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a dark gray background.</string>
	<key>BlueDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a light blue background.</string>
	<key>BlurryBlueLights</key>
	<string>Blue hued blurry lights on a dark background</string>
	<key>BrightYellowDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots on a bright yellow background.</string>
	<key>BubblesOnSurface</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of bubbles adhering to a clear surface.</string>
	<key>BunStyleHaircut</key>
	<string>iPod Wallpaper with woman silhouette sporting a bun style haircut.</string>
	<key>CalmLakeWithMountains</key>
	<string>Photo of a calm lake, with mountains in the distance and shooting stars in the sky.</string>
	<key>CalmWatersReceeding</key>
	<string>The calm waters of a lake receeding into the distance and merging with the horizon.</string>
	<key>CartoonRedFlowers</key>
	<string>Asian-style drawing of red flowers</string>
	<key>CarvedTotenFace</key>
	<string>Photo of a carved face on a totem pole</string>
	<key>Chalkboard</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of an erased chalkboard.</string>
	<key>CloseUpBladeGrass</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of thick blades of green grass.</string>
	<key>CloseUpDewDrops</key>
	<string>Thin blades of dark green grass with dew droplets interspersed along the blades.</string>
	<key>CloseUpGrass</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of grass with dew droplets on the tips of each blade.</string>
	<key>CloseUpWater</key>
	<string>Gentle ocean waves lap at eye level. The sky is bright near the water, but turns dark blue near the top of the photo.</string>
	<key>Cobblestones</key>
	<string>Photo of gray cobblestone surface.</string>
	<key>ColoredOverlappingPatterns1</key>
	<string>A melange of overlapping colors that form interlocking parallelograms, tilted to brighter hue.</string>
	<key>ColoredOverlappingPatterns2</key>
	<string>A melange of overlapping colors that form interlocking parallelograms, tilted towards a bluer hue.</string>
	<key>CrashingWave</key>
	<string>Photo of a large, crashing ocean wave.</string>
	<key>DancingWomanSilhouette</key>
	<string>iPod Wallpaper with dancing woman silhouette</string>
	<key>DarkDotsBlueBack</key>
	<string>Dark dots on a blue background</string>
	<key>DarkDotsPurpleBack</key>
	<string>Dark dots on a purple background</string>
	<key>DarkGrayDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a dark gray background.</string>
	<key>DarkGrayFlowerShapes</key>
	<string>Dark gray flower-shaped geometrical pattern</string>
	<key>DarkSandstoneRocks</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of dark sandstone rocks</string>
	<key>DarkStitchedSquarePattern</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a darkly colored piece of stitched cloth with square patterns.</string>
	<key>DarkStitchedVertPattern</key>
	<string>Photo of black fabric with white vertical pinstripes</string>
	<key>DarkerRedDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a stronger red background.</string>
	<key>DenimOneStitchClose</key>
	<string>Photo of blue denim with one vertical seam.</string>
	<key>DropletsInWater</key>
	<string>Expanding and overlapping concentric circles in a pool of water.</string>
	<key>EarthFromSpace</key>
	<string>Photo of the Earth from space.</string>
	<key>EarthHorizon</key>
	<string>The horizon of a cloudy planet floating in space.</string>
	<key>FlecksOfColors</key>
	<string>Flecks of color on a light blue parchment background.</string>
	<key>FlowerBallsOnLongStalks</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of flower with a yellow, spherical head on a long stalk.</string>
	<key>FrizzyHairedSilhouette</key>
	<string>iPod Wallpaper with frizzy haired woman silhouette</string>
	<key>FrothyWave</key>
	<string>A black and white photo of a frothy, turbulent ocean wave.</string>
	<key>GeodesicHexagons</key>
	<string>Interlocking three dimensional white hexagons within hexagons</string>
	<key>GeometricOrangeTriangles</key>
	<string>Oranged-hued geometric pattern of triangle and rhombus shapes.</string>
	<key>GeometricPurplishFlowerShapes</key>
	<string>Pink-hued geometric flower shaped designs arranged in a mosaic pattern.</string>
	<key>GoldOvalShapes</key>
	<string>Gold hued oval-shaped geometrical pattern</string>
	<key>GoldenGrassHills</key>
	<string>Lush green grass grows over a landscape of hills. A river snakes through the tall, undulating grass.</string>
	<key>GoldenPoppyFlower</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a California golden poppy</string>
	<key>GoldenPoppyFlowers</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of California golden poppies.</string>
	<key>GreenDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a green background.</string>
	<key>GreenPlantFrondsArt</key>
	<string>Green-hued drawing of the fronds of a plant.</string>
	<key>GreenWhiteCamo</key>
	<string>Green and white camouflage pattern.</string>
	<key>GreenishChalkboard</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of an erased chalkboard with a green hue</string>
	<key>LargeDotsBlackBack</key>
	<string>Large patterned dots on a black background.</string>
	<key>LightBlueDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a light blue background.</string>
	<key>LightGrayDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a light gray background.</string>
	<key>LightToDarkBlueGradient</key>
	<string>A gradient that transitions from dark blue at the top to pink at the bottom.</string>
	<key>LightYellowToGreenishGradient</key>
	<string>A gradient that transitions from light blue green at the top to tan at the bottom.</string>
	<key>MountainsTwilight</key>
	<string>Photo of mountains in the distance during twilight with water in the foreground.</string>
	<key>NebulaStars</key>
	<string>Deep space photo of a nebula gas cloud with many stars.</string>
	<key>NorthernLights</key>
	<string>The northern lights in a star filled sky. Streaks of bright blueish white lights punctuate a background of green haze.</string>
	<key>OceanWaterOnBeach</key>
	<string>Crystal clear water laps onto a pristine sandy beach.</string>
	<key>OverlappingSquares</key>
	<string>Two overlapping translucent squares with rounded corners. The squares transition between yellow and blue colors.</string>
	<key>PeacockTailFeather</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a peacock's tail feathers</string>
	<key>PinkDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a pink background.</string>
	<key>PurpleWhiteCamo</key>
	<string>Purple and white camouflage pattern.</string>
	<key>RecedingMountains</key>
	<string>Aerial photo of blue-tinged mountains receding into the distance.</string>
	<key>RedDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots on a red background.</string>
	<key>ReddishCirclesConnectedArtfully</key>
	<string>Red-hued overlapping circles in a geometric grid.</string>
	<key>RoseWithCobweb</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a budding pink rose with cobwebs</string>
	<key>RoseWithDewDrops</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a blossomed pink rose with dew droplets</string>
	<key>SlateWithStriations</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of flat slate with a variety of striations.</string>
	<key>SnowyMountains</key>
	<string>Snow covered mountains reaching into the sky. A river runs through a valley at the base of the mountains.</string>
	<key>SunsetHillsVista</key>
	<string>The morning sun stretches over rolling green hills that recede into the distance as mist gently rises.</string>
	<key>TidesOnBeach</key>
	<string>Ocean waves lapping gently on a sandy beach.</string>
	<key>TreeCrossSection</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a cross section of a cut tree.</string>
	<key>VerticalBarsWithHorizontalBars</key>
	<string>Light-tan horizontal lines with round ends staggered along vertical lines on a darker tan background.</string>
	<key>WaterLilly</key>
	<string>Close-up photo of a water lily.</string>
	<key>WhiteDots</key>
	<string>Many small gray dots floating on a white background.</string>
	<key>WinterLake</key>
	<string>Thin, leafless trees covered in snow in a glacial, placid blue lake during winter.</string>
	<key>WoodCirclesInShingleFashion</key>
	<string>A photo of circular wood shingles that have been stained to a pleasantly dark color.</string>
	<key>YellowBlueGradient</key>
	<string>A gradient that transitions from dark blue at the top to orange at the bottom.</string>
	<key>YellowDots</key>
	<string>Many small white dots floating on a yellow background.</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.blue.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a light blue hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.dark.blue.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a dark blue hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a blue hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.green.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a green hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.grey.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a grey hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.pink.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a pink hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.red.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a red hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.silver.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a silver hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.bokeh.yellow.description</key>
	<string>Floating circles at varying visual depths with a yellow hue</string>
	<key>dynamic.wallpapers</key>
	<string>Dynamic wallpapers</string>
	<key>pano.wallpapers</key>
	<string>Panoramic wallpapers</string>
	<key>parallax.wallpapers</key>
	<string>Parallax wallpapers</string>
	<key>still.wallpapers</key>
	<string>Still photo wallpapers</string>
	<key>wallpaper.table.cell</key>
	<string>Change wallpaper…</string>
</dict>
</plist>
