<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd">
<plist version="1.0">
<dict>
	<key>LOCATION_PRIVACY_DESCRIPTION_IPAD</key>
	<string>&lt;p&gt;
Location Services allows Apple and third-party apps and websites to gather and use information based on the current location of your iPad to provide a variety of location-based services. For example, an app might use your location data and location search query to help you find nearby coffee shops or theaters, or your iPad may set its timezone automatically based on your current location. To use features such as these, you must enable Location Services on your iPad &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; give your permission to each app or website before it can use your location data. For safety purposes, however, your iPad’s location information may be used for emergency calls to aid response efforts regardless of whether you enable Location Services.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Location Services uses GPS (where available) along with crowd-sourced %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations to determine your iPad’s approximate location. If Location Services is on, your iPad will periodically send the geo-tagged locations of nearby %2$@ hotspots and cell towers in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting this crowd-sourced database of %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations. By enabling Location Services, location-based system services such as these will also be enabled:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Traffic.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are physically moving (for example, traveling in a car), your iPad will periodically send GPS locations and travel speed information in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting a crowd-sourced road traffic database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Popular Near Me.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPad will periodically send locations of where you have purchased or used Apps in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to improve a crowd-sourced database that may be used to offer geographically-relevant Apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location-Based iAds.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPad will send your location to Apple in order to provide you with geographically relevant iAds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The crowd-sourced location data gathered by Apple does not personally identify you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
By enabling Location Services on your iPad, you agree and consent to the transmission, collection, maintenance, processing, and use of your location data and location search queries by Apple and its partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based and road traffic-based products and services.
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
You may choose to disable Location Services at any time. To do so, open Settings, tap Privacy, tap Location Services, and either turn off the global Location Services switch or turn off the individual location switches of each location-aware app or feature on your iPad. To disable Location Services for all websites, turn off the location switch for the Safari app. You may also disable location-based system services on your iPad by tapping on System Services and turning off the switch for each location-based system service on your iPad.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you allow third-party apps or websites to use your current location, you are subject to their terms and privacy policy and practices. You should review the terms, privacy policies, and practices of such apps and websites to understand how they use your location and other information. Information collected by Apple will be treated in accordance with Apple’s Privacy Policy, which can be found at www.apple.com/privacy.
&lt;/p&gt;
</string>
	<key>LOCATION_PRIVACY_DESCRIPTION_IPHONE</key>
	<string>&lt;p&gt;
Location Services allows Apple and third-party apps and websites to gather and use information based on the current location of your iPhone to provide a variety of location-based services. For example, an app might use your location data and location search query to help you find nearby coffee shops or theaters, or your iPhone may set its timezone automatically based on your current location. To use features such as these, you must enable Location Services on your iPhone &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; give your permission to each app or website before it can use your location data. For safety purposes, however, your iPhone’s location information may be used for emergency calls to aid response efforts regardless of whether you enable Location Services.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Location Services uses GPS (where available) along with crowd-sourced %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations to determine your iPhone’s approximate location. If Location Services is on, your iPhone will periodically send the geo-tagged locations of nearby %2$@ hotspots and cell towers in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting this crowd-sourced database of %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations. By enabling Location Services, location-based system services such as these will also be enabled:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Traffic.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are physically moving (for example, traveling in a car), your iPhone will periodically send GPS locations and travel speed information in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting a crowd-sourced road traffic database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Popular Near Me.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPhone will periodically send locations of where you have purchased or used Apps in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to improve a crowd-sourced database that may be used to offer geographically-relevant Apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frequent Locations.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPhone will keep track of places you have recently been, as well as how often and when you visited them, in order to learn places that are significant to you. This data is kept solely on your device and will not be sent to Apple without your consent. It will be used to provide you with personalized services, such as predictive traffic routing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location-Based iAds.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPhone will send your location to Apple in order to provide you with geographically relevant iAds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The crowd-sourced location data gathered by Apple does not personally identify you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
By enabling Location Services on your iPhone, you agree and consent to the transmission, collection, maintenance, processing, and use of your location data and location search queries by Apple and its partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based and road traffic-based products and services.
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
You may choose to disable Location Services at any time. To do so, open Settings, tap Privacy, tap Location Services, and either turn off the global Location Services switch or turn off the individual location switches of each location-aware app or feature on your iPhone. To disable Location Services for all websites, turn off the location switch for the Safari app. You may also disable location-based system services on your iPhone by tapping on System Services and turning off the switch for each location-based system service on your iPhone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you allow third-party apps or websites to use your current location, you are subject to their terms and privacy policy and practices. You should review the terms, privacy policies, and practices of such apps and websites to understand how they use your location and other information. Information collected by Apple will be treated in accordance with Apple’s Privacy Policy, which can be found at www.apple.com/privacy.
&lt;/p&gt;
</string>
	<key>LOCATION_PRIVACY_DESCRIPTION_IPOD</key>
	<string>&lt;p&gt;
Location Services allows Apple and third-party apps and websites to gather and use information based on the current location of your iPod to provide a variety of location-based services. For example, an app might use your location data and location search query to help you find nearby coffee shops or theaters, or your iPod may set its timezone automatically based on your current location. To use features such as these, you must enable Location Services on your iPod &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; give your permission to each app or website before it can use your location data. For safety purposes, however, your iPod’s location information may be used for emergency calls to aid response efforts regardless of whether you enable Location Services.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Location Services uses GPS (where available) along with crowd-sourced %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations to determine your iPod’s approximate location. If Location Services is on, your iPod will periodically send the geo-tagged locations of nearby %2$@ hotspots and cell towers in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting this crowd-sourced database of %2$@ hotspot and cell tower locations. By enabling Location Services, location-based system services such as these will also be enabled:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Traffic.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you are physically moving (for example, traveling in a car), your iPod will periodically send GPS locations and travel speed information in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to be used for augmenting a crowd-sourced road traffic database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Popular Near Me.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPod will periodically send locations of where you have purchased or used Apps in an anonymous and encrypted form to Apple, to improve a crowd-sourced database that may be used to offer geographically-relevant Apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location-Based iAds.&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Your iPod will send your location to Apple in order to provide you with geographically relevant iAds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The crowd-sourced location data gathered by Apple does not personally identify you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
By enabling Location Services on your iPod, you agree and consent to the transmission, collection, maintenance, processing, and use of your location data and location search queries by Apple and its partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based and road traffic-based products and services.
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
You may choose to disable Location Services at any time. To do so, open Settings, tap Privacy, tap Location Services, and either turn off the global Location Services switch or turn off the individual location switches of each location-aware app or feature on your iPod. To disable Location Services for all websites, turn off the location switch for the Safari app. You may also disable location-based system services on your iPod by tapping on System Services and turning off the switch for each location-based system service on your iPod.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
If you allow third-party apps or websites to use your current location, you are subject to their terms and privacy policy and practices. You should review the terms, privacy policies, and practices of such apps and websites to understand how they use your location and other information. Information collected by Apple will be treated in accordance with Apple’s Privacy Policy, which can be found at www.apple.com/privacy.
&lt;/p&gt;
</string>
	<key>LOCATION_PRIVACY_HOTSPOT_TYPE_WIFI</key>
	<string>Wi-Fi</string>
	<key>LOCATION_PRIVACY_HOTSPOT_TYPE_WLAN</key>
	<string>WLAN</string>
</dict>
</plist>
